Christmas at the Chalet is a tv movie, romance,
comedy film directed by Lucie Guest.
When ex TV host and socialite Lex finds herself faced with the possibility of spending Christmas sharing a luxury chalet with her son, ex husband and his new girlfriend, she
volunteers to work in the chalet to avoid things getting too close to home, while documenting her every move for a new wave of followers loving this new chapter of her life.
Lex Riley, played by Teri Hatcher.
George Hammond, played by Brendan McRae.
Charles Hammond, played by Dan Payne.
Liese, played by Gigi Neil.
Eric Tremblay, played by William deVry.
Celine Tremblay, played by Patti Allan.
Chalet Girl is a 2011 romantic comedy sports film directed by Phil Traill.
The film stars Felicity Jones and Ed Westwick in the lead roles and also features Ken Duken,
Tamsin Egerton, Sophia Bush, Bill Bailey, Brooke Shields, and Bill Nighy.
Written by Tom Williams, the film was produced by Pippa Cross,
Harriet Rees, Dietmar Guentsche, and Wolfgang Behr.
Chalet Girl was filmed on location in Sankt Anton am Arlberg,
Austria, and in Garmisch-Partenkirchen, Germany.
While critical reaction to the film was mixed, Jones' performance was praised.
The film grossed US$5.5 million worldwide against an
£8 million (US$13 million) budget.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.